{
  "level": 3,
  "unit": 6,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A person who ________with others gave them information or ideas.",
          "answer": "communicated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something ________is very important or necessary.",
          "answer": "essential"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________is something a person wants and tries to get or become.",
          "answer": "goal"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A person who is ________has a reason for doing something.",
          "answer": "motivated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ job requires special education.",
          "answer": "professional"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is the careful study of a topic to find and learn facts.",
          "answer": "research"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is ________, it is important.",
          "answer": "serious"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ knows a great deal about something.",
          "answer": "specialist"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "________ means afraid or frightened.",
          "answer": "alarmed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is a great suffering of the mind or agony.",
          "answer": "anguish"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ________ needs to be done, had, or used.",
          "answer": "necessary"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you are ________, you think about one thing all the time and nothing else.",
          "answer": "obsessed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you ________something, you have or own it.",
          "answer": "possess"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is something given or received in return for something done.",
          "answer": "reward"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ can be money, jewels, or anything else that is valuable.",
          "answer": "treasure"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "________ is a having a lot of money or valuable things.",
          "answer": "wealth"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "________ is something that interests and amuses a person.",
          "answer": "entertainment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ________ is funny and makes people laugh.",
          "answer": "humorous"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ________ is very silly or foolish.",
          "answer": "ridiculous"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that ________, slid or glided like a snake.",
          "answer": "slithered"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is a poem that tells a story.",
          "answer": "narrative poem"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Words that ________ end in the same sound.",
          "answer": "rhyme"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is a regular pattern of sounds that is repeated.",
          "answer": "rhythm"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ________ is a group of lines arranged in a pattern of rhyme or rhythm.",
          "answer": "stanza"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
